<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WorkAndTravel</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">About Work and Travel</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">States and Taxes</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">People\'s experiences</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Agencies</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Embassies</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="intro1">What is the Summer Work and Travel Program (SWT)?</string>
    <string name="intro2">The Summer Work and Travel program is designed for foreign post-secondary students to enter the United States on a nonimmigrant visa to work and travel for a maximum of four months during their summer vacation. Last year over 450 Jordanian students received Summer Work and Travel visas.</string>
    <string name="intro3">The Summer Work and Travel program is designed for foreign post-secondary students to enter the United States on a nonimmigrant visa to work and travel for a maximum of four months during their summer vacation. Last year over 450 Jordanian students received Summer Work and Travel visas.  Most participants typically work in non-skilled service positions at resorts, hotels, restaurants, and amusement parks. However, summer internships are allowed in other U.S. businesses and organizations including, but not limited to: architecture, science research, graphic art/publishing and other media communication, advertising, computer software and electronics, and legal offices. The term of the internship may not exceed the four-month program duration and must be completed during the student’s summer vacation. U.S. State Department regulations prohibit the placement of program participants as domestic help in U.S. households or in positions requiring them to invest their own money for inventory such as door-to-door sales. Students may choose to apply to the Summer Work and Travel Program through the approved agencies in the United States or one of the approved Jordanian agencies listed below.</string>
    <string name="intro4">\tDivan International \n \n Cosmopolitan World Wide Experience \n \n Stationcom  \n \n Institute of International Cultural Exchange</string>
    <string name="intro5">When is the Summer Work and Travel (SWT) Season for Jordan?"   </string>
    <string name="intro6">The 2018 SWT program dates are June 15, 2018 to October 15, 2018. It is important to note that all participants should return to Jordan when their university starts the next semester.</string>
    <string name="intro7">Who is eligible to participate in the SWT program?</string>
    <string name="intro8">Must be enrolled in a full-time course of post-secondary study* and pursuing a degree from an accredited educational institution</string>
    <string name="intro9">Must demonstrate they will continue studies after participating in SWT; and Seniors must show strong plans for graduate school or work in Jordan upon their return</string>
    <string name="intro10">Must demonstrate English proficiency at a level at which they can successfully perform their job and live in the United States.</string>
    <string name="intro11">Final year students are eligible to take part in this program during the school’s major academic break immediately following their graduation, as long as they apply to participate in the program prior to graduation.</string>
    <string name="intro12">Can students who are refused a SWT visa re-apply during the same SWT season?</string>
    <string name="intro13">Yes, a previous refusal for a tourist or other type of visa does not preclude you from applying for a SWT visa. However, the SWT program is designed for bona fide students. Students who cannot demonstrate that they returned to Jordan in time last year to begin their classes will be refused a visa.  Furthermore, if the student makes purposeful misstatements as to when he or she returned to Jordan or when school started, they could be found permanently ineligible for a U.S. visa. Those students interested in re-applying for a visa should be able to provide additional or new information that was not available during their previous interview. This information must exhibit a substantial change in their situation or eligibility for a SWT visa.</string>
    <string name="visa1">PREPARE FOR THE VISA INTERVIEW</string>
    <string name="visa2">After your DS2019 has been issued, you\'ll get a pre-visa interview orientation scheduled. Your consultant will send you a list of all the documents required.</string>
    <string name="visa3">It is crucial to get all of them in time for your orientation. Otherwise we won\'t be able to schedule a visa interview.</string>
    <string name="visa4">Documents needed for your Visa Interview Orientation:</string>
    <string name="visa5">International passport – original</string>
    <string name="visa6">Completed DS160 – access link and instructions for completing will be provided by your consultant.</string>
    <string name="visa7">Picture – size 5х5. On paper and a digital version on a USB stick</string>
    <string name="visa8">Receipt for paid visa interview fee.</string>
    <string name="visa9">A copy of your Job Offer</string>
    <string name="visa10">Certificate of Enrollment from your university – issued for the current semester.</string>
    <string name="visa11">Student book</string>
    <string name="visa12">Copies of your previous USA visas – if you have any.</string>
    <string name="visa13">ATTEND THE VISA INTERVIEW</string>
    <string name="visa15">You\'ll know the exact date and time of your interview a few days after your visa orientation.</string>
    <string name="visa16">Do not be late for your interview! The US Embassy will not agree to reschedule it unless you prove a serious issue.</string>
    <string name="visa17">Get to the Embassy half an hour before the interview. Bring the Confirmation page from your orientation and a picture ID with you.</string>
    <string name="visa18">How does the interview go?</string>
    <string name="visa19">You\'ll go through a security check before entering the building. Do not bring liquids, weapons or sharp objects. All electronics should be switched off and turned to the security officers. Bring as few possessions as possible. Do not take pictures.\n\nAfter the security check, you will enter the Embassy building. There\'ll be representatives to guide. You\'ll wait for your fingerprints to be taken, and receive your documents /the ones that we have prepared on the visa interview orientation/.</string>
    <string name="visa20">At the time of the interview:</string>
    <string name="visa22">Keep calm</string>
    <string name="visa23">If you don\'t hear a question, ask the consul to repeat it</string>
    <string name="visa24">Do not lie</string>
    <string name="visa25">How will you receive your visa?</string>
    <string name="visa26">Three days after the interview, you will be able to pick up your passport with the printed visa in it from the nearest TNT office. You should visit your Orange office after you take your documents.</string>
    <string name="doc1">DS-2019</string>
    <string name="doc2">The DS-2019 form is a government-controlled document that gives you the opportunity to apply for a J1 visa. This document together with your J1 visa allows you to legally live and work in the United States. You can find the exact period of time you are permitted to work in the States in section 3 of the form. Bear in mind that you have additional 30 days after the end of your work period, when you are permitted to stay in the States as a tourist. Working, however, in this 30-day grace period is prohibited and illegal.</string>
    <string name="doc3">documents icon J-1 VISA</string>
    <string name="doc4">The J-1 visa is a non-immigrant visa that gives you the right to enter, work and live in the United State of America for a certain period of time. As soon as you successfully pass the visa interview, this document will be placed in your passport.Issue Date - this is the date you were being interviewed in the US Embassy.

Expiration Date - this is the last date you are permitted to work in the States. This date can also be found on your DS 2019 form (section 3). It does not include the 30 days travel period.

Remember you should return on time for the beginning of your university classes.
</string>
    <string name="doc5">I-94</string>
    <string name="doc6">Going through U.S. Customs and Border Protection (\"Immigration\") is the first thing you\'ll do upon arrival in USA. Their rep will scan your passport and your personal data will be submitted to their system. That includes date of entry, visa type and duration of stay.  Immediately after that you\'ll be able to get your I-94 number by logging to this address: https://i94.cbp.dhs.gov/.  Make sure you save this number because you\'ll need it several times during your program.</string>
    <string name="doc7">SEVIS</string>
    <string name="doc8">Student Exchange Visitor Information System (SEVIS) - was first put to use in 2003 by the US Government. This system is a huge data base, containing up-to-date information about all exchange students, who are temporary in the States. A lot of US services and institutions such as Sponsor organizations, Immigration services, Embassies, etc. are able to enter the system.  Your top priority after arrival is to register with SEVIS. You must register within 3 days of your arrival. It\'s easy and takes less than 10 minutes. You will be asked to provide the date you have entered the States, the number of your I-94 form and the address where you will be living during your Work and Travel.  Timely registering in SEVIS guarantees you will have a good standing with the US Immigration services.  You\'ll be using a defferent website to check-in with SEVIS depending on your sponsoring organization:</string>
    <string name="doc9">\tIntrax \n United Work and Travel \n Janus International</string>
    <string name="doc10">Do not try to register with SEVIS from your home country! Trying it before you enter the States may lead to problems. You may even be forbidden entrance.</string>
    <string name="doc11">Change of address</string>
    <string name="doc12">You must contact your US sponsor organization within 48 hours to provide them with your new address. You cannot use a company address or a PO. Box.</string>
    <string name="doc13">Change of work</string>
    <string name="doc14">You must contact your US sponsor organization and wait for an approval prior to changing your employer. Only after you are allowed to change your work place, you can leave your current employer with no negative consequences for you.</string>
    <string name="doc15">MEDICAL INSURANCE</string>
    <string name="doc16">As a participant in a Work and Travel program, you are required to have a medical insurance. This insurance covers both sickness and accidents that might take place during the exchange visitor program.</string>
    <string name="doc17">If Medical Assistance is required at any time please call the Toll free line 1 800 840 9749</string>
    <string name="doc18">SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER</string>
    <string name="doc19">Briefly after you checkin with SEVIS you can apply for a Social Security number. See an example of a Social Security Number.  All people who are permitted to legally work in the States must have a Social Security Number (SSN). This is a nine digit number that is issued by the Social Security Administration.  A Social Security Number has lifetime validity. If you have participated in a Work and Travel program before and you already have a SSN, you do not need to apply again.  Start by locating the nearest Social Security Administration Office</string>
    <string name="doc20">Necessary documents when applying for a SSN:</string>
    <string name="doc21">International passport - (original + 1 copy)</string>
    <string name="doc22">Visa - (original + 1 copy)</string>
    <string name="doc24">DS 2019 Form - (original + 1 copy)</string>
    <string name="doc25">Job Offer</string>
    <string name="doc26">Social Security Application Form (SS-5) (scroll bellow for instructions)</string>
    <string name="doc27">Another picture ID (personal ID, diving\'s license)</string>
    <string name="doc28">When applying for a Social Security Number (SSN), ask the clerk for a document, certifying your application. Writing down their name, the date you applied for a social security card and the address of the administration office is also useful.</string>
    <string name="doc29">SS-5</string>
    <string name="doc30">You need this form in order to apply for a Social Security Number.</string>
    <string name="doc31">How to fill-in the SS-5 form:</string>
    <string name="doc32">Line 1 - write down your FULL name as written on your passport.\n\nLine 2 - leave blank\n\nLine 3 - write down the name of your birth city as it appears in your passport\n\nLine 4 - fill-in your date of birth, using the mm/dd/yyyy format\n\nLine 5 - choose \"Legal Alien Allowed to Work\"\n \nLines 6, 7, and 8 - tick the boxes that describe you\n\nLine 9A - write your mother\'s maiden name (her name at birth)\n\nLine 9B - leave blank\n\nLine 10A - write your father\'s full name\n\nLine 10В - leave blank\n\nLine 11 - put a mark at “No”\n\nLines 12 and 13 - leave blank\n\nLine 14 - write down the date that you are applying for a Social Security Number\n\nLine 15 - write down the phone number of your US employer\n\nLine 16 - write down the address where you would like to receive your SSN card. I advices to fill the full address of your US employer (must be written correctly)\n\nLine 17 - sign the form\n\nLine 18 - mark the field that says \"Self\". Do NOT fill anything after that line!</string>
    <string name="doc33">It takes 4 to 6 weeks for your Social Security Card to be issued. During this period you are legally permitted to work only with the employer indicated on your DS-2019 form. If you haven\'t received your Social Security Number in 8 weeks time contact the administration at: 1-800-772-1213</string>
    <string name="doc34">If by any reason you do not get your SSC at the address you have indicated in your Social Security Application you can request a reissue.</string>
    <string name="doc35">W-4</string>
    <string name="doc36">On your first days at work your employer will provide you with two forms that you need to fill-in: W-4 and I-9. Both documents are important for your right taxation.  The W-4 form determines what amount of taxes will be deducted from your paycheck. Almost all of the instructions for the W-4 form are aimed at American residents. Since your tax status in the States is \"Non-Resident Alien\", we advise you to fill in the following information:</string>
    <string name="doc37">Page</string>
    <string name="doc38">Line 1: fill-in your full name the way it is written in your passport (Make sure your writing is legible and without mistakes) and the address of your Work and Travel agency, or your home country address\n\nLine 2 you are supposed to write down your Social Security Number. If it is still processing, leave the field blank\n\nLine 3 thick off \"Single\"\n\nLine 4 - make a thick only in necessary\n\nLine 5 - write 1 (one)\n\nLine 6 - write 0 (zero)\n\nLine 7 - Do NOT write \"EXEMPT\"  Sign and date the document</string>
    <string name="doc39">Lines A and H - write 1 (one);  Leave lines B,C, D, E, F and G empty.</string>
    <string name="doc40">I-9</string>
    <string name="doc41">The I-9 form (Employment Eligibility Verification) informs the Federal Government you\'re allowed to work legally. See a sample I-9 here. You are supposed to fill-in only Section 1 of this document. We advise you to:\n\nWrite your full name (exactly as it appears in your passport),start with your Family name. Write your US address, date of birth (mm/dd/yyyy), City, State, P.O. Box and Social Security Number, leave blank if you haven\'t received it yet.\nTick off “An alien authorized to work until” and then copy the expiration date of your DS-2019. Then write down either your I-94 number or Passport number and the country it was issued in.\n\nYour employer will fill-in sections 2 and 3 of this form.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="callStr">Call</string>
    <string name="mailStr">Send Mail</string>
    <string name="webStr">Visit there website</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="str1">1. Budget and plan ahead</string>
    <string name="str2">You may have finalized your job and accommodations for the summer, but if you haven’t budgeted for daily as well as unexpected expenses, you’re missing the biggest piece of your travel puzzle. Start estimating your cost of living expenses now to ensure you can cover those unexpected expenses, as well as avoid overpaying for your basic expenses.</string>
    <string name="str3">Some of our former participants have been caught off-guard by some of these expenses, including:\n\nPhone bills: Your mobile service is your responsibility, so make sure you’ve budgeted enough for local service. You’ll have several options for staying in touch while abroad.\n\nHousing: Many participants find that their housing accommodations are not furnished. Don’t forget to bring some money to buy basic amenities at the beginning of your trip.</string>
    <string name="str4">2. Learn the language</string>
    <string name="str5">One of the fastest ways to get comfortable in a new country is by speaking the local language. If you dedicate some time to practicing your English before arriving in the USA, you’ll be better equipped to work with your host employer, make new American friends, and find out about local events in your town. If you hear a phrase or a slang word you don’t understand, don\'t be afraid to speak up and ask what it means!</string>
    <string name="str6">3. Embrace the culture around you</string>
    <string name="str7">Your new host community will undoubtedly be exciting for the first few weeks, and a few frustrations here and there won’t spoil your enthusiasm. But many participants deal with culture shock when they first arrive in the U.S. Trying to understand different values and unfamiliar habits can be tough. Remember that you’re not alone in dealing with these feelings, but there are also effective ways to cope with culture shock.</string>
    <string name="str8">4. Pack the right clothes</string>
    <string name="str9">One of the biggest surprises you might find in the USA is that the weather can vary wildly: a warm day on the coast of Maine, for instance, will likely be cooler than a warm day in Virginia Beach. Research your placement location ahead of time and check both the daytime and nighttime temperature of your destination, as well as the expected weather for each month. Make sure you also have a set of clothes for different kinds of weather conditions: you may spend much of your time in a dry climate, but you’ll wish for a rain jacket if you travel to Florida in August.</string>
    <string name="str10">5. Get to know your community</string>
    <string name="str11">Americans are famously friendly, so don’t be afraid to attend community events! InterExchange often works with local communities to organize cultural events. These events are a great opportunity to make new friends, meet the local people, and get a unique insight into American culture. If you’ve never attended a baseball game, participated in a volunteer event, or enjoyed an American pizza party, these events are your gateway!</string>
    <string name="str12">6. Don\'t forget any necessary medications</string>
    <string name="str13">Medical care is notoriously expensive in the U.S. and some over-the-counter medications are no exception. Save your spending money for your post-travel period, and carry any necessary medicines with you: contact lens solution, etc. Keep in mind some additional medical expenses (like copays or emergency room visits) may not be covered by your insurance and you’ll have to pay the amount out of your pocket. Budget for at least one visit to the doctor or, if you can, one ER visit.</string>
    <string name="str14">7. Consider your banking options</string>
    <string name="str15">Don’t leave money on the table. No matter how strong your home currency is, research the exchange rate before you leave home and try to get the best exchange rate possible if you are bringing cash to the U.S.  If you are using your bank account from your home country, ask the bank what they charge for overseas use. You could also open a local bank account in the U.S.\n\nto avoid all additional international charges. Our banking guide outlines what you can expect when you open an account and the documents you will need.</string>
    <string name="str16">8. Be a savvy traveler</string>
    <string name="str17">Whether you\'re planning a weekend getaway or a long road trip during your travel period, follow these tried-and-true travel tips from past participants:\n\nTransit: We’ve all been there: we’ve misplaced our baggage or your airline lost your checked luggage.Don’t ruin your otherwise well-planned trip: Keep a change of clothes, important documents, and any other essentials in your carry-on luggage.\n\nDriving: A great way to explore the U.S. is by going on a great American road trip. You should make sure to get an international driving license before coming here. Be aware of the rules and regulations. Get familiar with driving in the U.S. and see if are eligible to get a local driving license.\n\nLong weekends and holidays: If you want to travel during holiday weekends between May and September - Memorial Day, Fourth of July, or Labor Day - make sure you budget accordingly. Traveling during those days can be expensive, and you’ll find that car rental rates and airfare may drastically increase. Use our travel resources that could give you some helpful tips depending on where your travel plans.</string>
    <string name="noteStr">Feel free to post your experience with other!</string>
    <string name="strH1">your name</string>
    <string name="strH2">your country</string>
    <string name="strH3">where have you been in the us?</string>
    <string name="strH4">Tell us about it</string>
    <string name="strUpload">Upload a photo</string>
    <string name="strpublish">Publish it</string>
    <string name="strCansel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="arabicStr">For arabic explanation click here !</string>
    <string name="ar1">- برنامج تبادل ثقافي في الولايات المتحدة الامريكية، يحصل الطالب من خلاله على عقد عمل\"مش في تخصصه\" بقدر من خلاله يشتغل ويحصل على راتب بالإضافة انه بكون متأمن بسكن وتأمين صحي</string>
    <string name="ar2"> البرنامج خلال فترة الصيف فقط ومسموح العمل في الفترة من 1-6 ولغاية شهر 10 تقريبا.</string>
    <string name="ar3">متى ببلش و كم مدته؟</string>
    <string name="ar34">شروط البرنامج</string>
    <string name="ar5">تكون طالب جامعة او بكالوريس او دكتوراهو مخلص بحدود ال 30 ساعة</string>
    <string name="ar6">معدلك يكون فوق ال2  يفضل يكون فوق ال2.3 او ال65٪؜</string>
    <string name="ar7">ما تكون خريج يعني بس ترجع من البرنامج يكون ضل عليك ساعات.</string>
    <string name="ar8">شو طبيعةالشغل؟</string>
    <string name="ar9">الشغل بكون اشي ما اله علاقة بتخصصك، زي فندق، مطعم، مول، مدينة ملاهي، مدينة مائية، كافيه، منقذ سباحة...</string>
    <string name="ar10">كم الراتب وكم ساعات الشغل بتكون؟</string>
    <string name="ar11">الراتب هناك بالساعة والرواتب بتعتمد على الولاية ومكان الشغل بشكل أساسي\n بس تقريباً اغلب الرواتب بتكون 8-12 دولار بالساعة\n عدد الساعات بالأسبوع بيعتمد على شغلات كثير بس بالعادة يكون 32-40 ساعة.</string>
    <string name="ar12">مين بيدفع أجار السكن؟</string>
    <string name="ar13">باغلب العقود بكون السكن مأمن بس الطالب الي بيدفع الأجار، وبعقود قليلة جدا يكون السكن مجاناً</string>
    <string name="ar14">وتكلفة السكن بتعتمد على المكان بس تقريبا من 50-100 دولار بالأسبوع.</string>
    <string name="ar15">شو نوع ال VISA و هل هي سهلة و كيف مقابلة السفارة؟</string>
    <string name="ar16">نوع الفيزا J1، وتعتبر من أسهل الفيز ونسبة قبولها جدا عالية، مقابلة السفارة كل سنة بتعمل ايفنت وينشرح عنها بشكل مطول بس بشكل عام الموضوع ما بيخوف</string>
    <string name="ar17">معدلي تحت ال 2.3 ممكن انقبل؟</string>
    <string name="ar18">أكيد ممكن بس فرصتك اقل، من كم سنة كان كثير طلاب معدلهم ٢ وينقبلوا، بس جديد صار الموضوع أصعب،\n بس برأيي الموضوع يستحق شرف المحاولة</string>
    <string name="ar19">لغتي ضعيفة عادي؟</string>
    <string name="ar20">اه أكيد، البرنامج من أهدافه تحسين لغة الطالب، المقابلة بالسفارة بتكون بالإنجليزي والمطلوب منك تكون بتعرف اساسيات المحادثة وتعرف تجاوب على الأسئلة الي يسألها القنصل والموضوع جدا سهل، وأي طالب وصل الجامعة المفروض يعرف يدبر اموره.</string>
    <string name="ar21">كم تكلفة البرنامج؟</string>
    <string name="ar22">البرنامج تقريبا بيكلف 1300 الى 1400 للمكتب، 113 دينار للسفارة\n و تذكرة الطيران 50 الى 700 دينار تقريبا \nبالإضافة انه الطالب بده يعمل حسابه بمصروف اول فترة.</string>
    <string name="ar23">كم ممكن ارجع من البرنامج وهل صحيح أني رح اجيب مصاري كثير وأحقق كل أحلامي!</string>
    <string name="ar24">الموضوع بختلف من شخص ل شخص وكل واحد اله تجربة مختلفة، في طلاب رجعت من البرنامج خسرانه وعليها فلوس و في طلاب رجعت معها فلوس كثير و في طلاب رجعت الفلوس الي دفعتها و رجعت بملغ إضافي، الفئتين الأولى والثانية عددهم جدا جدا جدا قليل خصوصًا الثانية و الاغلب بكون من الفئة الثالثة، عشان هيك ما حد يعلق اماله وطموحاته على البرنامج لانه رح يتعذب نفسياً و غالبا ما تزبط معه، بس زي ما حكيت الأغلب برجع المبلغ الي دفعه بالإضافة لمبلغ اضافي</string>
    <string name="ar25">بقدر اشتغل شغل ثاني ؟</string>
    <string name="ar26">أكيد اغلب الطلاب بتعمل هيك لكن في بعض العقود يكون فيها الموضوع صعب حسب طبيعة العمل و المكان.</string>
    <string name="ar27">متى التقديم ببلش ومتى بنتهي؟</string>
    <string name="ar28">التقديم بلش من شهر 8 و بنتهي بس تخلص المقاعد، الموضوع يختلف من سنة ل سنة بس اذا ناوي لا تاخر الموضوع و سجل بأسرع وقت.</string>
    <string name="ar29">في بنات شاركوا بالبرنامج وهل الموضوع آمن؟</string>
    <string name="ar30">باخر سنتين عدد البنات المشاركات زاد بشكل كبير،  من ناحية الأمان، بالبداية البنت بدها تكون قد حالها لانه في شباب راحت هناك وما كملت أسبوعين، من ناحية الأمان، امريكا قارة وفي مليون مكان سيء و مليون كمان منيح، بدها تختار مكان مناسب ك طبيعة عمل و ولاية و يفضل انها تبعد عن ولايات الجنوب، وتروح ع الأماكن الي معروفة بتواجد العرب والمسلمين فيها،</string>
    <string name="ar31">كم بخسر اذا انرفضت؟</string>
    <string name="ar32">في حال الرفض من السفارة بتقدر ترجع تقدم اكثر من مرة بس في حال قررت تنسحب من البرنامج بعد ما انرفضت رح يرجعلك كامل المبلغ الي دفعته الا ( 275- 400) دينار حسب المكتب بالإضافة لرسوم السفارة.</string>
    <string name="strFace">Facebook Page</string>
    <string name="addressStr">Address:</string>
    <string name="strTitle">Work and Travel</string>
    <string name="strBout">About</string>
    <string name="strAbout">This app was created to tell the students about Work and travel program in the usa , and to guide them in their journey </string>
    <string name="strPolicy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="shareStr">Share and Rate</string>
    <string name="strList">Things you have to check before you travel</string>
</resources>
